Yehonatan Roumani

Full Stack Web Developer

Phone number: 054-214-0173 | Email: jonathanroumani@gmail.com

Education:

Ariel University

John Bryce

B.Sc., Industrial engineering, 2005 - 2009 Dean's List September 2006 Full Stack Web Developer, 2018-2019

About me:

In current position I have been working in a well-established company on a big project to move their website to a new and updated design. This included a broad use of CSS, HTML, jQuery, PHP and JavaScript. My previous experience in account managing and managing the development of a web system with clients brings a big advantage when building new products as a developer.

Technical Skills:

- Full Stack developer with knowledge in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express, React, Redux, Angular, MySQL, MongoDB and Mongoose.
- A passion for building web systems.

Experience:

2020-present - Web Developer at PlaySmart

 Working directly under the CTO to update and implement a redesign to the company's website. Using PHP, JavaScript, CSS, HTML and WordPress.

2018-2019- Founder - AdopSolutions

- Developed a SaaS solution for affiliate networks to automate their optimization of mobile CPI campaigns.
- Responsible for the product vision, planning and design. Set roadmaps and product backlog. managed 3 programmers and managed the business and marketing side.

2016-2018- Account Manager - AirPush

• Introduced and built AirPush CPI division and Demand API. Integrated new demand and supply into the system and managed the daily operations and monthly billing.

2014-2016 Account Manager - StartApp

- Helped build and forge the StartApp Market division.
- Setting up hundreds of affiliate and advertisers accounts. Creating thousands of campaigns. Using advanced features in groups and targeting with a strong knowledge in tracking.

2013 Regional Manager for Jerusalem Mayor Nir Barkat's Municipal Elections

• Recruiting and management of a team of over 20 field reps whom I trained to work with a unique survey application that was built especially for the campaign.

2011 -2013 Sales Manager at A1 Solar Power

• Directly responsible for A-Z sales cycle with residential and commercial clients resulting in over \$300,000 in annual revenue.

2009 – 2010 Material Planner at Sanmina-SCI

• Responsible for Sanmina's material requirement planning of electric and mechanical components valued at one million dollars quarterly. Developed and implemented process control which resulted in savings of thousands of dollars, reducing the quantities of inventory.

Military Service:

Israeli Defense Force – Sergeant. Special operations unit Maglan, commanders' course. 2001-2004

<u>Languages:</u> Hebrew – Native. English - Native